Where are you looking?
どこ見てるの?
I was here, now.
ここに居たんだけど、今
Didn't you notice?
気づかなかった?
It's been a while.
久しぶりですね
久しぶりです
Thank goodness it's sunny today.
よかった、今日晴れて
I'm fine.
元気いいです
How have you been lately?
最近元気してた?
I was fine.
元気だったです
Ah, I love this honey.
あ、このハチミツ好きなんだよね
Something with honey and fruit mixed together is delicious.
なんかね、ハチミツとフルーツが一緒に混じってるやつが美味
Yes.
しい
Would you like to see it?
見て みる?
It's delicious, isn't it?
美味しいですよね
Try it and see if it's delicious.
ちょっと美味しいか食べてみてよ
Which would you like to eat?
食べるとしたらどれがいい?
Yes, what kind of flavor is it?
そう、どんな味のり?
Oh, do you like fruit?
あ、フルーツ好き?
Well then, since this is so bad, let's destroy it.
じゃあこれ、こんなにバッテマイだから壊しようか
Try eating this.
食べてみてよ、これ
The fruits look delicious.
フ ル ーツ美味しそう
Do you like fruit?
フルーツ好き?
Please give me this.
これください
It will be available in a box.
お箱入りの方でご用意します
Ah, I'll give you this.
あ、これあげる
thank you.
ありがとう
Well, you can have soda or something,
これさ、ソーダとかがあってもいいし、
Do you like Yo Food?
ヨーフード好き?
Okay then.
じゃあいいね
Okay, it's tough.
いいよ、つらい
This is what I'm curious about.
こう気になるんだよ
thank you.
ありがとう
This is a toy store.
おもちゃ屋さんじゃん、これ
nostalgic.
懐かしい
Will you see something?
なんか見てくる?
I'll try going back.
帰ってみる
This is it, this.
これなんだ、これ
Oh, this is huge.
あ、これ、でっかくね
This is amazing.
すごいね、これ
Okay, so that's it.
よし、じゃあもうこれだ
Buy this, buy this.
これ買って、これで買っちゃおう
Let's buy this.
これで買っちゃおう
Should I go to the park?
公園行ってやると良いか
yes.
はい
I.
私
How much do you sell that ball?
そこの玉はどれくらい売り?
picture?
え?
Elementary school student?
小学生?
That's right.
だよね
Because I'd be scared if I did it.
やっちゃったら怖いから
Shall we sit over there?
あそこ座って 座ろうか
fun?
楽しい?
That guy is amazing.
すごいね、あの人
Water is running all the time.
ずっと水出してるよ
I'm hungry.
お腹すいたね
Let's eat.
食べようよ
What did you do?
何にした?
In the end, I was told that it didn't look like Ogura.
結局ね、なんか おぐらしかないって言われたから
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Did you eat red bean paste?
あんこ食べた?
amazing.
すごい
Did you write it?
書いたの?
delicious?
おいしい?
I haven't eaten red bean paste yet.
まだあんこ食べれてない
It hasn't come out that far.
あんこまで出てきてない
Can you do this?
これでできるの?
Try patter patter.
パタパタパタってやってみて
It's done, it's done.
できたできた
Awesome, amazing.
すごいすごい
This is amazing.
すごい これ
nice.
いいね
This is huge.
でっかいのできるね、これ
fun?
楽しい?
Awesome, amazing.
すごいすごい
Amazing amazing.
すごい すごい
Ippa
いっぱ
Yes, I can.
い できる
amazing.
すごい
Full of that life.
その生いっぱい
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
照れくさいね、
Something.
なんか
This is a Gillis skirt that I would love to wear.
これ 着たいぐらいギリスカーツだもんね
yes.
そう
The one doing it.
やってるやつ
I guess I'm better at binding than you.
お前よりも 縛りよくなったんじゃない?
Not here.
ここじゃないよ
Did you exercise?
運動した?
Yeah, it's not falling.
うん、落ちてない
TRUE?
本当?
I feel like I'm gaining muscle.
筋肉増えてる気がする
That's not true.
そんなことない
Doesn't it look like a photo shoot?
撮影っぽくない?
Get out like this.
こうやって抜けて
If you make it look like this.
みたい な感じにすると
It's the best.
最高ですね
Embarrassing child, show me this.
恥ずかしい子、こっち見せて
I'll do this when I'm facing down.
下向いたらこうするよ
I'll go for a little while.
もうちょっと行くって
Can I comb your hair?
髪の毛くっしらってもいい?
That's just it.
ちょうどあれだね
It's long enough to not get caught.
引っかからない長さだね
Chikubi, chikubi, chikubi.
チクビ、チクビ、チクビ
Go 10 times.
ビクチって10回行って
Did you understand?
分かっちゃった?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Shall I take this off?
これ脱いちゃう?
cute.
かわいい
Are you mesmerized?
見とれちゃう?
Do you want to dilute it?
薄めたい?
Yeah.
うん
Can I join?
入会っていい?
yes.
そう
I'll put it somewhere safe.
安全なところに置いてあげる
It's called punch.
パンチってやつだね
punch.
パンチ
Get on there.
そこに乗って
Can you hold your own legs?
足自分で持ってくれる?
It's kind of stained.
なんかシミになってる
It's stained.
シ ミになってるよ
I took it off, but this too.
脱 がしたけどね、これも
Hold it like this.
持っててこうやって
I'll make you take off your clothes in an embarrassing way.
恥ずかしい格好で脱がせるんだから
ray.
えい
I took it off.
脱いちゃった
all.
全部
You're shaking, just a little.
震えてるよね、ちょっとね
Want to take it off quickly?
早く脱ぎたい?
Oh no, this look.
やだ、この格好
It's nice though.
素敵なんだけど
Well, I feel sorry for you, so I'll take it off.
じゃあ、可哀想だから脱がしてあげる
It's a little dark, go over there.
ちょっとまっくら、そっち行って
Because it's narrow.
狭いから
Head over there.
そっちに頭根っこ上がって
Mamo, can I observe?
まも、観察していい?
a little bit.
ちょっと
I want to make a little observation.
ちょっと観察したい
Okay, yes.
よし、はい
Relax, relax.
リラックス、リラックス
Relax.
リラックスして
Does it smell really bad?
いっちゃいにおいする?
a little bit.
ちょっと
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Are you feeling good?
気 持 ち いい の?
Maybe I should lick it.
ペロペロしようかな
Do you not like it?
嫌なの?
Will you bite me?
噛んでくれる?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
How many more times should I watch it?
もっと何回見る?
It became extremely crunchy.
すごいビシャビシャになっちゃった
Do you know this?
これ知ってる?
Do you know?
知ってる?
i don't know?
知らない?
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Okay, do you want it?
よし、ほしい?
Is that enough?
もういいの?
what
なん
in?
で?
Would you like to lick this dick?
こ っちのチンチ舐める?
Can you do it while licking my dick?
チンチ舐めながらやってくれる?
My hands are so cold.
すごい手、冷えてる
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Let's do six stuns.
シックスタンしよう
Let's be excited.
ワックレしよう
Can you come here?
こっち来れる?
Okay.
よし
It's the previous shape.
前 の形したよね
Is today okay too?
今日もいい?